<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>airdrops.io</title>
	<atom:link href="https://airdrops.io/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://airdrops.io/</link>
	<description>Your Trusted Crypto Intelligence Hub: From Airdrops to Advanced Strategies</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 11:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/apple-touch-icon-152x152-150x150.png</url>
	<title>airdrops.io</title>
	<link>https://airdrops.io/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Al]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airdrop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bartio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bartio testnet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bera]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[berachain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[testnet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=894764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Introduction to Berachain Berachain is an emerging blockchain network that has garnered significant attention in the cryptocurrency space. With a substantial $142 million investment from reputable venture capital firms, Berachain ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/#more-894764">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/">Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Introduction to Berachain</h2>



<p><strong>Berachain</strong> is an emerging blockchain network that has garnered significant attention in the cryptocurrency space. With a substantial $142 million investment from reputable venture capital firms, Berachain introduces a novel consensus mechanism called Proof of Liquidity (POL). This innovative approach sets it apart from traditional Proof of Work (PoW) and Proof of Stake (PoS) systems.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Understanding Proof of Liquidity (POL)</h2>



<p>Unlike Bitcoin&#8217;s PoW or Ethereum&#8217;s PoS, Berachain&#8217;s POL mechanism allows users to participate in network security and transaction processing by locking liquidity on the network. This unique approach not only ensures network stability but also inherently increases the Total Value Locked (TVL), benefiting the ecosystem&#8217;s overall health.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Key Tokens in the Berachain Ecosystem</h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>BERA</strong>: The native token used for gas fees and network transactions.</li>



<li><strong>HONEY</strong>: A native stablecoin within the Berachain network.</li>



<li><strong>BGT</strong>: A governance token earned through providing liquidity, which can be delegated for voting rights.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Airdrop Farming Strategy for Berachain</h2>



<p>To position yourself for potential airdrops, consider the following strategies:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">1. Increase Transaction Count</h3>



<p>Aim for 200-300 organic transactions, with some users targeting up to 500. This activity demonstrates genuine engagement with the network.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">2. Utilize Faucets Effectively</h3>



<p>Berachain&#8217;s team has emphasized the importance of faucets in this testnet. Key faucets include:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><a href="/visit/64t2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bartio Faucet</a> (8-hour cooldown)</li>



<li><a href="/visit/6xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Kodiak Finance Faucet</a> (3-hour cooldown)</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">3. Provide Liquidity and Farm BGT</h3>



<p>Use acquired BERA to provide liquidity on <a href="/visit/7xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bex</a>, focusing on pools with high APY. This strategy allows you to earn BGT, a non-tradable token crucial for potential airdrop qualification.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">4. Engage with the Ecosystem</h3>



<p>Interact with various Berachain platforms:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><a href="/visit/8xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Station</a> for BGT farming and delegation</li>



<li><a href="/visit/vxp2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Honey</a> for minting the network&#8217;s stablecoin</li>



<li><a href="/visit/9xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bend</a> for borrowing</li>



<li><a href="/visit/axt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">BERPS</a> for perpetual trading</li>



<li>Beranames: It is the official name service for Berachain, offering a human-readable address system for blockchain transactions. Users can mint unique NFT names, personalize their Berachain ID, and create subdomains for contracts, wallets, and more.<br>Beranames is running a points campaign for its early users, which may factor into future airdrops when Berachain goes live. Participating in the Beranames ecosystem demonstrates active engagement and could potentially increase your chances of qualifying for future airdrops.<br>For a detailed guide on how to participate in Beranames and earn points, refer to <a href="https://airdrops.io/beranames/">our comprehensive guide</a>.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">5. Diversify Transactions</h3>



<p>Use <a href="/visit/bxt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Intract</a> for varied transaction types, ensuring a well-rounded activity profile.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">6. Discord Engagement</h3>



<p>Join the <a href="https://discord.gg/berachain" target="_blank">Berachain Discord</a> and actively participate in community channels. Engage thoughtfully to potentially receive BERA tips from community whales.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">7. Claim and Delegate BGT</h3>



<p>Regularly claim your farmed BGT and delegate it to validators, demonstrating long-term commitment to the network&#8217;s governance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Berachain&#8217;s innovative POL mechanism and robust ecosystem present unique opportunities for airdrop farmers. By engaging genuinely across various platforms, providing liquidity, and actively participating in the community, you can optimize your chances for potential future rewards.</p>



<p>Remember, while these strategies can enhance your position, there&#8217;s no guarantee of airdrops. Always conduct your own research and invest responsibly. Also make sure to read our full Airdrop Guide <a href="https://airdrops.io/berachain/">Here</a>.</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/">Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>“I Didn’t Hear No Bell”: Tactics for ZKsync’s 2nd Round</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/tactics-for-zksync-round-2/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/tactics-for-zksync-round-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 15:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[zksync]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=760823</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Token price down bad! ZK farmers REKT! A handful of farmers are defiant, barely standing on their feet and are stating that they “didn’t hear no bell”. If you also ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="“I Didn’t Hear No Bell”: Tactics for ZKsync’s 2nd Round" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/tactics-for-zksync-round-2/#more-760823">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">“I Didn’t Hear No Bell”: Tactics for ZKsync’s 2nd Round</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/tactics-for-zksync-round-2/">“I Didn’t Hear No Bell”: Tactics for ZKsync’s 2nd Round</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Token price down bad! ZK farmers REKT! A handful of farmers are defiant, barely standing on their feet and are stating that they “didn’t hear no bell”. If you also have the courage to continue with ZK and refuse to hear any bell, it could be handsomely rewarded. Read on to find out how you can step in the ring for a 2nd round.</p>
<p>First, let’s recap: Round 1 dropped just over 3.6 billion ZK (which is the native token of <a href="/visit/wg82/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">ZKsync</a> that was <a href="/visit/slr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">airdropped</a> to users in June). That leaves just over 10.3 billion ZK tokens that are guaranteed to be distributed to users in the near future. And there’s potentially even more that can be earned from protocols that share their tokens from airdrop #1.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-760838 size-large" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-distribution-1024x691.png" alt="" width="1024" height="691" srcset="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-distribution-1024x691.png 1024w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-distribution-300x203.png 300w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-distribution-768x518.png 768w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-distribution-1536x1037.png 1536w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-distribution.png 1600w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>Three different tactics will be explained that will help you get the most out of the 10.3 billion ZK tokens that are left:</p>
<ol>
<li>Governance drops: HODL and delegate (6.135B ZK tokens)</li>
<li>Protocol initiatives from airdrop #1 (~26.7M ZK confirmed so far; potentially up to 1.2B ZK)</li>
<li>Ecosystem initiatives (4.179B ZK tokens)</li>
</ol>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Governance Drops: HODL and Delegate</h2>
<p>The first and easiest way to position for ZK round 2 is to HODL your allocation and delegate for governance.</p>
<p>The <a href="/visit/g0q2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">ZK token blog post</a> mentions:</p>
<blockquote><p>“The rest will be distributed over time, through <strong>ecosystem initiatives</strong>, managed by the ZKsync Foundation, and the <strong>ZK Nation governance process</strong>, to support a growing ecosystem as new users come on chain.”</p></blockquote>
<p>From this, it can be deduced that another airdrop will occur, most likely for users who never sold their ZK and delegated to governance. But the governance drop could also apply to any address that delegates a certain amount of tokens for a specified period of time.</p>
<p>If you weren’t eligible for airdrop #1, buy at least 971 ZK tokens, HODL and delegate for governance. Do it urgently and see it as a long-term investment in ZKsync as an ecosystem. Why?</p>
<p><strong>Because it’s very likely that ZKsync will rerun the playbook from Optimism’s airdrop #2 and #3.</strong></p>
<p><em>If you haven’t delegated your ZK yet, you can do it <a href="/visit/7lr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a>.</em></p>
<p>As a result, you should HODL and delegate at least 917 ZK tokens. Didn’t receive the first drop? Buy and delegate a minimum of 917 ZK. With a current price of around ~$0.17, 917 ZK amounts to around $156.</p>
<p>As a refresher, Optimism dropped OP tokens to active users in May 2022. Then in February 2023, after more than 90 governance proposals were voted on, a surprise <a href="/visit/8lr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">airdrop #2</a> was announced. Anyone actively engaged in governance by delegating tokens received up to 5,000 OP! The 2nd round rewarded users based on “token days delegated”, using the following threshold:</p>
<p><em>Number of tokens delegated x Days delegated &gt; 2,000</em></p>
<p>For example, a user who delegated 50 OP for governance only had to do so for at least 41 days to be eligible, since 50 x 41 &gt; 2,000. Multipliers were also awarded for addresses that had delegated the minimum allocation from airdrop #1 for at least 200 days, as well as those that had a larger amount of OP tokens delegated.</p>
<p>Delegating for governance was rewarded yet again with <a href="/visit/h8q2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">airdrop #3</a> on September 18th, 2023. Again, the allocation was determined by the ‘token days delegated’, but this time with an upper limit of 10,000 OP airdropped per address!</p>
<p>The main takeaway is that ZKsync is very likely to do something similar to Optimism and there may be multiple rounds of governance-related airdrops. We predict that in the next 12 months, there’ll be at least one ZK airdrop that’s related to governance. It’s very likely the same criteria will be used: a certain threshold set for ‘token days delegated’.</p>
<p>To position for the governance portion of a ZK round 2:</p>
<ul>
<li>If you don’t HODL ZKsync’s token already, buy at least 971 ZK and delegate for governance.</li>
<li>Depending on how bullish you are on ZK, buy and delegate more tokens to active governance participants for as long as possible to earn a potentially larger allocation in the 2nd round.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Protocol Initiatives from Airdrop #1</h2>
<p>The other ways to qualify for more ZK are through the ecosystem and protocol initiatives which could total a maximum of 5.397 billion ZK: up to 1.218B from ZKsync native protocols that received the airdrop #1 and 4.179B from ZKsync as part of ecosystem initiatives.</p>
<p>That’s the 5.8% from the pie chart shown below, plus the 19.9% for the ecosystem initiatives in the previous pie chart.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-760839 size-full" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-airdrop-1.png" alt="" width="1024" height="691" srcset="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-airdrop-1.png 1024w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-airdrop-1-300x202.png 300w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/zk-airdrop-1-768x518.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p>But, in practice, the actual number of ZK up for grabs will be somewhat lower.</p>
<p>Not all ZKsync native protocols are going to share their entire allocation with users. And some are not even sharing any at all! So how much of that 5.8% of the token supply flows into the hands of users is unknown at the moment.</p>
<p>Only 8 projects have so far confirmed that 100% of their allocation from airdrop #1 will be shared with their communities, amounting to almost 29.2 million ZK. Izumi Finance and PancakeSwap have already started distributing their tokens to users, leaving approximately 24.3 million ZK.</p>
<p><img decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-760836 size-full" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-11-at-16.56.22.png" alt="" width="538" height="670" srcset="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-11-at-16.56.22.png 538w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-11-at-16.56.22-241x300.png 241w" sizes="(max-width: 538px) 100vw, 538px" /></p>
<p>Some of the protocols that have committed 100% to users include:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/tevaera/">Tevaera</a>: 30% of their ZK tokens have already been distributed to top players who didn&#8217;t receive the ZK airdrop. The remaining tokens are dedicated to rewards for all Tevans who participate in future initiatives.</li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/syncswap/">Syncswap</a>: No plans made public yet. Provide liquidity and swap regularly.</li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/koi-finance/">Koi Finance</a>: No plans made public yet. Provide liquidity, buy and lock their token, and swap regularly.</li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/grvt/">GRVT</a>: Participate in their reward program.</li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/reactor-fusion/">Reactor Fusion</a>: 50% was distributed to RLP Season 0 participants, The remaining 50% will be used to incentivise borrowers and lenders until September 15th.</li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/pancakeswap/">PancakeSwap</a>: 53.5% was distributed to veCAKE holders and past users. The ZK tokens left over will be used to reward LPs and traders until June 2025.</li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/vest/">Vest</a>: No plans made public yet. Provide liquidity and make 2-3 trades per week to potentially become eligible.</li>
</ul>
<p>Other projects have hinted at rewarding users, but haven’t made a full commitment to give their communities 100% of their allocations. These are <a href="https://airdrops.io/kelp-dao/">Kelp DAO</a> (use rsETH on ZKsync) and <a href="https://airdrops.io/ether-fi/">EtherFi</a> (bridge/use weETH on ZKsync once it launches).</p>
<p>DeFi heavyweights with high TVL and adoption like Aave, <a href="https://airdrops.io/ethena/">Ethena</a>, Lido, Lens, Curve, Cronos and Frax Finance got the largest ZK ecosystem allocations. Taken together, these projects account for 47.48M ZK. Interact with these protocols once they launch on ZKsync and monitor their socials for any announcements. It’s likely that the majority, if not all, of these ZK tokens will be used to boost the APRs for liquidity providers. Unless you can provide a lot of liquidity ($50K-$100K+), it’s best to focus on more niche projects that reward users with airdrops that are transaction based or depend on metrics other than liquidity, such as <a href="https://airdrops.io/grvt/">GRVT</a>, <a href="https://airdrops.io/tevaera/">Tevaera</a>, and/or <a href="https://airdrops.io/zkcandy/">zkCandy</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Ecosystem Initiatives</h2>
<p>Ecosystem initiatives can be grouped into two speculative categories, rewarding users who are:</p>
<ol>
<li>New users of Elastic chains</li>
<li>Loyal ZKsync users</li>
</ol>
<p>A total of 4.179B ZK tokens will be distributed by the ZKsync Foundation to projects, then from projects to users.</p>
<h3>New Users of Elastic Chains</h3>
<p>Perhaps the most important ecosystem initiative will be the launch of various Elastic chains. <a href="/visit/9lr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Elastic chains</a> are basically a network of different zkRollups that are interoperable with one another.</p>
<p>Several important implementations to keep an eye on in the upcoming months are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Lens Network (and <a href="/visit/alr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">mint your Lens profile</a> if you haven’t got one already!)</li>
<li>Cronos zkEVM</li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/grvt/">GRVT</a></li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/zkcandy/">zkCandy</a></li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/zerion/">ZERO</a></li>
<li><a href="https://airdrops.io/airdrop/sophon/">Sophon</a></li>
</ul>
<p>Using Optimism again as a case study, Elastic chains are basically ZKsync’s take on the Superchain (OP Stack chains like Base and Mode). The emergence of Optimism’s Superchain, a network of chains built using the OP Stack also gave rise to new airdrop farming opportunities and tokens, such as MODE.</p>
<p>There’s a high likelihood that each Elastic chain launch will bring us a new airdrop farming opportunity, with confirmed token drops for GRVT and zkCandy. However, there’s less clarity on airdrops or tokens from other Elastic chains.</p>
<h3>Loyal ZKsync Users</h3>
<p>Since many farmers have dumped their ZK tokens and departed from ZKsync in search of other opportunities, a smaller pool of players remain.</p>
<p>With less competition and sybil activity, it’s beneficial to maintain an active on-chain footprint on ZKsync. Also, qualifiers for future airdrops may be relaxed to reward the genuine and loyal user base, especially now that most sybil farmers should be elsewhere.</p>
<p>Daily active addresses are at a 14-month low and transaction counts are also falling. The severely sharp decline is exactly what you want to see if you’re planning to farm ZK’s round 2.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="aligncenter wp-image-760835 size-large" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-17-at-14.36.04-1024x344.png" alt="" width="1024" height="344" srcset="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-17-at-14.36.04-1024x344.png 1024w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-17-at-14.36.04-300x101.png 300w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-17-at-14.36.04-768x258.png 768w, https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2024/07/Screenshot-2024-07-17-at-14.36.04.png 1359w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Source: <a href="/visit/blr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">https://www.growthepie.xyz/fundamentals/daily-active-addresses</a></em></p>
<p>When looking at the on-chain data, one conclusion that follows: the crowd’s consensus is that the ZK airdrop is done, it’s time to move on to other opportunities and never look back. At a first glance, the mercenary element seems to have focused elsewhere, rather than continuing on with ZKsync.</p>
<p>Despite this outflow of active users, the potential for ZKsync to benefit from the so-called “Lindy effect” is high. ZKsync’s mission and vision are closely related to security and privacy, and very much closer in ethos to the roots of Bitcoin and Ethereum as compared to many other projects in our view, this is another good reason to hang around for further rounds.</p>
<p>This is excellent news for people who intend to continue with ZKsync, or want to start farming the 2nd round. Genuine on-chain usage after the hype has died down and commitment to the protocol’s success could be signalled by users that remain through their on-chain activities.</p>
<p>Here’s a list of important actions that should form the base of your strategy for ZK’s 2nd round:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Transaction count</strong>: 2 or 3 transactions per week should suffice.</li>
<li><strong>Transaction volume</strong>: try to generate at least $100 in volume per week.</li>
<li><strong>Paymaster transactions</strong>: use paymaster supported tokens as gas when swapping at least 2 times per week. <a href="/visit/clr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Paymaster</a> is a feature unique to ZKsync that enables users to pay transaction fees in tokens other than ETH.</li>
<li><strong>dApp usage</strong>: pick 1-2 dApps and go HARD on them. Easiest ones are <a href="https://airdrops.io/tevaera/">Tevaera</a> for gamers and <a href="https://airdrops.io/vest/">Vest</a> for a passive strategy.</li>
<li><strong>Active weeks/months</strong>: use <a href="/visit/rlr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Owl.to’s daily check-in feature</a> as a cost effective way to remain active on a daily, weekly or monthly basis. Returning to the case study of Optimism airdrop #2, addresses with dApp transactions over 6 distinct months received a multiplier. So it could pay off to interact with dApps on zkSync every month for the rest of 2024.</li>
<li><strong>Number of unique contract interactions</strong>: aim for as many as possible. Try new protocols, use existing protocols you’ve never used before, mint NFTs on <a href="/visit/g6m2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Rhino.fi</a> and deploy your own ERC-20 token using <a href="/visit/dlr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Merkly</a>.</li>
<li><strong>Spend more than $20 on gas fees</strong>: this was another multiplier for Optimism’s airdrop #2. Although it’s less likely to be a criteria for ZK round 2, it’s worth being aware of this potential multiplier.</li>
<li><strong>Follow <a href="/visit/elr2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Airdrops.io on X</a></strong>, join the <a href="https://t.me/airdrops_io" target="_blank">Telegram channel</a> and monitor the <a href="https://airdrops.io/speculative/zksync/">ZKsync airdrop page</a> for any new protocols that launch.</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>“I Didn’t Hear No Bell”</h2>
<p>Apart from the price of ZK, ZKsync itself is not down and out. There’s no better time to start farming further rounds and secure your share of the remaining 10.3 billion tokens. Never miss the big picture. ZKsync is an innovative project that has one of the largest mindshares in the crypto space and one of the fairest distributions seen in recent years.</p>
<p>To summarise, follow these steps to position for ZK’s 2nd round:</p>
<ul>
<li>HODL at least 917 ZK and delegate for governance. Delegate a larger amount for a potential multiplier and higher allocation.</li>
<li>Pick at least 1-2 protocols that have committed 100% of their ZK tokens to their communities and become a power user.</li>
<li>Follow <a href="/visit/p0q2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">ZKsync Foundation on X</a> for updates on the ecosystem initiatives, which will likely be geared towards users of Elastic chains and dApps.</li>
<li>Remain active on-chain: push at least 1-2 dApp transactions and 1-2 Paymaster swaps every month.</li>
</ul>
<p>By following the tactics laid out above, readers should be well positioned for decent allocations in the near future.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p><em>Please note that this article does not constitute financial advice and is only presented for educational purposes. Always do your own research before buying cryptocurrencies and interacting with DeFi protocols.</em></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/tactics-for-zksync-round-2/">“I Didn’t Hear No Bell”: Tactics for ZKsync’s 2nd Round</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/tactics-for-zksync-round-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=650827</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ZkSync was the most highly anticipated airdrop in recent years and one of the most generous, distributing 17.5% of the total supply to eligible users and builders. While over 6 ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/#more-650827">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/">A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZkSync was the most highly anticipated airdrop in recent years and one of the most generous, distributing 17.5% of the total supply to eligible users and builders. While over 6 million wallets interacted with zkSync’s Layer 2, just over </span><a href="/visit/g0q2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">695,000 wallets were included</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Despite many missing out, ZK is one of the most widely distributed airdrops. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s not over for ZK farmers though. A further 49.5% of the supply will go to the community. In an upcoming post we’ll outline how to position for these further drops. In this post, we’ll take a look at 5 lessons from the ZK airdrop to see what farmers can learn from this event and how they can apply these takeaways to other Layer 2’s that are yet to </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">tokenize</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #1: Bridge In and Bridge Often, But Don’t Bridge Out</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZK took a serious departure from the playbook of other Layer 2 airdrops, such as Arbitrum. Transaction volume was not a qualifier at all! What they did introduce however, which we haven’t really seen much of in airdrops up until now, is a multiplier based on your time-weighted average balance (TWAB). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A TWAB approach favours smaller farmers who have less funds as compared to previous airdrops. It opens up the possibility that users with smaller pockets can maintain a larger TWAB than a mercenary farmer with more capital who only parked funds on zkSync for a much shorter time period. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specifically, zkSync users needed a time-weighted average balance of $50 to qualify, with a larger TWAB boosting to their allocation. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The few lessons farmers should take from this: </span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Users who stick around are rewarded: When bridging funds to a Layer 2, try to keep your funds there for as long as possible.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s a marathon, not a sprint: Bridge an initial amount and then bridge more funds over time. </span></li>
<li>Actively participate in DeFi protocols: Deposit these funds into a DeFi liquidity pool to earn yield and increase your chances of qualifying.</li>
</ol>
<h2><b>Lesson #2: HODL native tokens and NFTs</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Always buy and HOLD native tokens and NFTs for the Layer 2s you’re farming. You can use </span><a href="/visit/aoq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeFiLlama</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to see the top protocols for the chain you’re farming and see if they have a token. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZkSync users who held $50 or more in native tokens received a multiplier, specifically the top 7 projects ranked by market capitalisation. Another multiplier was given if a ZkSync native NFT collection was held at snapshot. On top of both of these actions, you should also trade at least 10 different ERC-20 tokens on the L2s you’re farming, as this was an eligibility criteria for ZK. </span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #3: Turn on Notifications on X for the Project You’re Farming</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As well as DeFiLlama, you can also turn on notifications for the official account of a Layer 2 on X to see what they post about. They’ll often promote native tokens and NFT collections. It’s recommended to take action based on what a project tweets about, as these can be subtle hints of which on-chain activities may be rewarded with an airdrop.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For example, the </span><a href="/visit/boq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">official zkSync account</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on X frequently tweeted about Paymaster function, which allows you to pay gas fees with tokens other than ETH. Many airdrop farmers speculated that using Paymaster frequently would be a possible criteria or multiplier, and they turned out to be right! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Similarly, you want to see what the official account of a Layer 2 is promoting and act on these cues to bag a larger airdrop!</span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #4: Be active on-chain and try new things</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A total of 102.375 million ZK tokens were distributed to experimental, on-chain communities, highlighting the importance of being active on-chain and trying new things. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BONSAI and DEGEN claimers both got a ZK allocation for simply being early to innovative on-chain communities. BONSAI was airdropped to certain Lens ecosystem users, a web3 social media alternative to Twitter and YouTube. DEGEN is the unofficial coin of Farcaster, another decentralized social media platform which awarded early adopters. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&#8217;s difficult to be early in the next big thing! But you should always be on the lookout, be active on-chain and try new things to maximise your airdrop exposure. You never know what interactions may end up giving you an unexpected surprise later down the line. </span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #5: Attend Crypto Events and Acquire POAPs</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Did you know that some people receive ZK tokens without being active on-chain? If you had attended one of seven events where zkSync was giving away POAPs, then you could have gotten a higher allocation. POAPs are short for proof of attendance protocols and they are on-chain badges proving you were at an event. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For example, if you had visited ZkSync’s booth at ETH Denver and collected the POAP, you’d have been eligible for the builders allocation. Some of these events even happened after the snapshot. For example, addresses that held POAPs from smaller events, like the zkSync meetup in Brussels, were also given a token allocation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The takeaway from this is that you should look to attend upcoming events, such as </span><a href="/visit/coq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">EthCC</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in Brussels (July 8th-11th). It&#8217;s likely that many teams from tokenless projects will be present and there will be many POAPs to collect. Alternatively, you can look for events closer to home by using sites like </span><a href="/visit/doq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">EventBrite</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="/visit/eoq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meetup</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and also by monitoring a project’s X account. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZkSync gives us yet another case study for airdrops, along with Arbitrum and StarkNet, that provides very useful information on what to focus on when farming the upcoming tokens for L2s like </span><a href="https://airdrops.io/scroll/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scroll</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://airdrops.io/linea/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Linea</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or </span><a href="https://airdrops.io/karak/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Karak</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. By taking these 5 lessons and applying them to your farming, you should have no problems qualifying for the next big drops! </span></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/">A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 10:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=9887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a schedule showing the dates of distribution for all of the Airdrops.io exclusive airdrops. ICOs that host airdrops almost never distribute tokens until their main sale is over. This ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/#more-9887">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/">Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is a schedule showing the dates of distribution for all of the Airdrops.io exclusive airdrops.</p>
<p><div id="tablepress-2-scroll-wrapper" class="tablepress-scroll-wrapper">

<table id="tablepress-2" class="tablepress tablepress-id-2 tablepress-responsive">
<thead>
<tr class="row-1 odd">
	<th class="column-1">Project</th><th class="column-2">Airdrop Started</th><th class="column-3">Distribution Date</th><th class="column-4">Link</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody class="row-hover">
<tr class="row-2 even">
	<td class="column-1">ImmVRse</td><td class="column-2">06/19/2018</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/immvrse/">ImmVRse</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-3 odd">
	<td class="column-1">HelloGold</td><td class="column-2">06/09/2018</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/hellogold/">HelloGold</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-4 even">
	<td class="column-1">Profede</td><td class="column-2">05/15/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/profede/">Profede</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-5 odd">
	<td class="column-1">EthicHub Twitter</td><td class="column-2">04/17/18</td><td class="column-3">After end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/ethichub-twitter/">EthicHub Twitter</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-6 even">
	<td class="column-1">EthicHub Telegram</td><td class="column-2">04/05/18</td><td class="column-3">After end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/ethichub/">EthicHub Telegram</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-7 odd">
	<td class="column-1">dApp Builder</td><td class="column-2">04/19/18</td><td class="column-3">After end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/dapp-builder/">dApp Builder</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-8 even">
	<td class="column-1">Pecunio</td><td class="column-2">04/05/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/pecunio/">Pecunio</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-9 odd">
	<td class="column-1">Lamoneda</td><td class="column-2">05/24/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/lamoneda/">Lamoneda</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-10 even">
	<td class="column-1">BitRewards</td><td class="column-2">04/06/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/bitrewards">BitRewards</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-11 odd">
	<td class="column-1">Apollo Currency</td><td class="column-2">04/30/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/apollo-currency/">Apollo</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-12 even">
	<td class="column-1">Hyperbridge</td><td class="column-2">06/23/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/hyperbridge/">Hyperbridge</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-13 odd">
	<td class="column-1">moolyacoin</td><td class="column-2">06/22/18</td><td class="column-3">2 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/moolyacoin/">moolyacoin</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-14 even">
	<td class="column-1">Blackbox Foundation<br />
</td><td class="column-2">02/07/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/blackbox-foundation/">Blackbox Foundation<br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-15 odd">
	<td class="column-1">ODIN</td><td class="column-2">12/07/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/odin/">ODIN</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-16 even">
	<td class="column-1">Beam</td><td class="column-2">06/08/18</td><td class="column-3">30 days after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/beam/">Beam</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-17 odd">
	<td class="column-1">RedCab</td><td class="column-2">14/08/18</td><td class="column-3">30 days after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/redcab-exclusive/">RedCab</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-18 even">
	<td class="column-1">dClinic</td><td class="column-2">20/08/18</td><td class="column-3">2 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/dclinic/">dClinic</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-19 odd">
	<td class="column-1">XTribe</td><td class="column-2">22/08/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/xtribe/">XTribe</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-20 even">
	<td class="column-1">IUNO</td><td class="column-2">10/09/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/iuno/">IUNO</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-21 odd">
	<td class="column-1">Triphop</td><td class="column-2">11/09/18</td><td class="column-3">5 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/triphop/">Triphop</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-22 even">
	<td class="column-1">MorLabs</td><td class="column-2">11/09/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/morlabs/">MorLabs</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-23 odd">
	<td class="column-1">AIVON</td><td class="column-2">20/09/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/aivon/">AIVON</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-24 even">
	<td class="column-1">HiLynk</td><td class="column-2">8/10/18</td><td class="column-3">6 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/hilynk/">HiLynk</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-25 odd">
	<td class="column-1">London Block Exchange<br />
</td><td class="column-2">12/10/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/london-block-exchange/">London Block Exchange<br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-26 even">
	<td class="column-1">V Systems</td><td class="column-2">06/11/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/v-systems/">V Systems<br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-27 odd">
	<td class="column-1">FST Network<br />
</td><td class="column-2">06/12/18</td><td class="column-3">6 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/fst-network/">FST Network <br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-28 even">
	<td class="column-1">Bluenote</td><td class="column-2">13/12/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/bluenote/">Bluenote <br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-29 odd">
	<td class="column-1">VANM</td><td class="column-2">19/12/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/vanm/">VANM<br />
</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-30 even">
	<td class="column-1">NOIA Network<br />
</td><td class="column-2">1/5/19</td><td class="column-3">3 months  after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/noia-network/">NOIA Network<br />
</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-31 odd">
	<td class="column-1">COINCOME</td><td class="column-2">10/7/19</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/coincome/">COINCOME<br />
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

</div><!-- #tablepress-2 from cache --></p>
<p>ICOs that host airdrops almost never distribute tokens until their main sale is over. This is to prevent airdrop claimers from dumping their rewards on decentralized exchanges and decimating the token&#8217;s price before the real investors have a chance to trade. Also, the total supply of a token us often determined after the token sale, when all unsold tokens are burned.</p>
<p>If you did not receive your airdrop tokens, you should check our FAQ section, &#8220;<a href="https://airdrops.io/faq/why-didnt-i-receive-my-airdrop/">Why didn&#8217;t I receive my airdrop?</a>&#8220;</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/">Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top Five Crypto Hardware Wallets: Review and Comparison</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/top-five-crypto-hardware-wallets-review-and-comparison/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/top-five-crypto-hardware-wallets-review-and-comparison/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 01:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=9248</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you own large amounts of coins, we highly recommend investing in a hardware wallet. Hardware wallets are the most secure way to store your precious cryptocurrencies. They have vital ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="Top Five Crypto Hardware Wallets: Review and Comparison" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/top-five-crypto-hardware-wallets-review-and-comparison/#more-9248">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">Top Five Crypto Hardware Wallets: Review and Comparison</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/top-five-crypto-hardware-wallets-review-and-comparison/">Top Five Crypto Hardware Wallets: Review and Comparison</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you own large amounts of coins, we highly recommend investing in a hardware wallet. Hardware wallets are the most secure way to store your precious cryptocurrencies. They have vital security features such as scrambled PIN codes and offline storage. They typically cost between $90 and $200.</p>
<p>Sadly, the majority of cryptocurrency users leave their coins vulnerable on exchanges or online wallets such as Coinbase. While this is certainly the most convenient option, it provides very little protection in the event that the exchange or wallet is hacked. It also makes it impossible to recover lost data since you do not have control of your private keys.</p>
<p>When dealing with cryptocurrencies, it is always better safe than sorry. There is no institution such as a bank who will protect you from a thief or scammer so once your funds are lost they are gone for good. Depending on your needs, certain cryptocurrency wallets are better than others. For most cryptocurrency holders, the <a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/ledger/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Ledger Nano S</a> or <a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/trezor/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Trezor</a> will be the best option, due to their ease of use for daily transactions, and impeccable security for long-term holding.</p>
<p>This may seem pricey, but hardware wallets are a one-time investment that will keep you secure for the long term. Think of it as a safe.</p>
<p>Here is a comparison of several well-known hardware wallets:</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Ledger Nano S</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-9613" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/ledger-nano-s.jpg" alt="" width="766" height="430" /><br />
<em>image via Worldwide Wallets</em></p>
<p>The <a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/ledger/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Ledger Nano S</a> is the most popular hardware wallet at the hardware wallet on the market due to its competitive pricing, good reputation, and the fact that it supports many coins. It is a sleek device resembling a USB drive and it is very simple to use. They are sold on the <a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/ledger/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">official Ledger site</a> for €79.</p>
<p>We do <strong>not</strong> recommend purchasing a Ledger Nano S from third-party resellers. There have been reports of resellers infecting Ledgers with malware to steal private keys. It is best to order directly from Ledger.</p>
<h3>How does the Ledger work?</h3>
<p>The functionality of the Ledger Nano S is quite simple. Data is accessed with the microchip inside of the device which is protected by a PIN code. Any outgoing transactions from the device must be confirmed with the physical press of a button, ensuring that no one can access your funds remotely even if your computer or access point is infected with malware.</p>
<p>Additionally, the Ledger Nano S ensures that all sensitive data is contained within an isolated component of the microchip so your private keys cannot be stolen.</p>
<h3>What if your Ledger is lost or stolen?</h3>
<p>Luckily, if your Ledger is ever lost you can easily recover your funds with the seed phrase that you will copy upon setup. Any thief who may have found you Ledger will have no way of accessing your funds without knowing the PIN code of the device. After a few failed PIN attempts, the device will wipe itself locally and erase all data.</p>
<h3>Does it only store Bitcoin?</h3>
<p>The Ledger Nano S stores a vast array of coins including favorites such as Bitcoin, Ethereum, Ripple and ERC20 tokens. Here is the full list of supported coins:</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-9612 aligncenter" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/ledgercoins.png" alt="" width="688" height="292" /></p>
<h3>How do I use my Ledger Nano S?</h3>
<p>The Ledger Nano S can be set up and operated from any computer with a USB port. When connecting your Ledger for the first time, you will need to download the <a href="/visit/3mg/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Google Chrome Ledger manager app</a>.</p>
<p>The Ledger has two buttons on it which correspond to up or down and are used to navigate the menus. Click both at once for “Select.”</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Trezor</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-9614" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/trezor_featured.jpg" alt="" width="757" height="397" /><br />
<em>image via Trezor.io</em></p>
<p><a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/trezor/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Trezor</a> is another classic hardware wallet with a long reputation for creating quality devices. Trezors sell for slightly more than the Ledger Nano S, at a price of €89.</p>
<h3>Why is Trezor so secure?</h3>
<p>Trezor’s unique PIN code provides incredible security. The device shows a scrambled series of numbers when the PIN is required, and the user must select the corresponding numbers on a blank box shown on their computer screen. This system of blindness and randomness prevents anyone from stealing your PIN even if they have already hacked your computer.</p>
<p>Trezor also features two-factor authentication that can be applied to add additional security. The most common procedure used is the Time-based One-Time Password (TOTP) which features random authentication codes scrambled every few seconds.</p>
<h3>What if I lose my Trezor?</h3>
<p>Trezor provides you with a recovery seed upon setup, so you can easily recover your funds if the device is lost. Thanks to the blockchain, you will never lose your private keys or transaction history.</p>
<h3>How do I use the Trezor wallet?</h3>
<p>When you initiate a transaction, a request is sent through the Trezor which requires a digital signature. The Trezor will display the transaction information including amount and destination address. The transaction must be validated by two physical clicks from the user, ensuring that the funds can never be transferred remotely.</p>
<p>Trezor supports the following cryptocurrencies:</p>
<ul>
<li>Bitcoin</li>
<li>Litecoin (LTC)</li>
<li>BCash (BCH)</li>
<li>Ethereum (ETH)</li>
<li>Ethereum Classic (ETC)</li>
<li>Dash (DASH)</li>
<li>Zcash (ZEC)</li>
<li>Dogecoin (DOGE)</li>
<li>ALL ERC-20 tokens</li>
</ul>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>KeepKey</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-9615" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/keepkey-featured.jpg" alt="" width="637" height="267" /><br />
<em>image via Buy Bitcoin Worldwide</em></p>
<p><a href="http://airdrops.io/goto/keepkey" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Keepkey</a> is a minimalist hardware wallet costing $129. It provides added security to actions such as private key generation, storage, and transaction signing. This hardware wallet generates its own private keys with the assistance of a number generator which uses randomization factors provided by actions of the user. This ensures that there is no pattern to the keys and that they are truly random.</p>
<h3>Keepkey Recovery Phrase</h3>
<p>Keepkey provides a 12-word seed phrase by default, but longer passphrases can be used if desired. We think that a 12-word seed is sufficient, but the longer your phrase, the more secure it will be. The passphrase can be used to recover all information from your wallets if the device happens to be lost or broken.</p>
<p>Keepkey is sleek and easy to use, but it does not support as many coins as the rest, and it is relatively expensive when compared with the Ledger Nano S.</p>
<p>Keepkey currently supports the following coins:</p>
<p>Bitcoin, Litecoin, Dogecoin, Namecoin, Testnet, Ethereum, and Dash</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>OpenDime</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-9616" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/opendime-featured.jpg" alt="" width="282" height="282" /><br />
<em>image via Crypto Cousins</em></p>
<p><a href="/visit/trg/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">OpenDime</a> is a lesser-known hardware wallet which is sold in packs of three for $37.50. They are quite unique in design and operation. OpenDime aims to be “cash for the crypto world,” where instead of handing someone cash, you could simply hand over an OpenDime. That said, it is geared more toward in-person transactions than long-term holding.</p>
<p>To set up the OpenDime, plug it into your USB port on your computer. The setup guide is available in a readme file that should appear upon connection. It will request for you to submit a file which will be used to randomize a new private key.</p>
<p>Once the key is created, load the OpenDime with the desired coins. The private key will remain untouchable until it is “opened.” An OpenDime can be physically opened with a small item such as a dime which will expose the private key.</p>
<p>Once opened, it can be plugged back into a computer to access its contents.</p>
<p>From the official OpenDime website, here are some situations in which an OpenDime may be useful:</p>
<ol>
<li>Gifting someone a Bitcoin! Preload an OpenDime and mail it to a friend.</li>
<li>Deliver the payment for a car when you go to pick it up. Just put your payment on an OpenDime and hand it over when you get the keys. Private key for car keys!</li>
<li>Load a number of OpenDimes with various denominations of Bitcoin. Keep them in your pocket to pay for things throughout your day.</li>
<li>Sell OpenDimes, preloaded with value, in exchange for gold or other precious metals.</li>
<li>Use this instead of a paper wallet. Just as “compatible” but takes care of generating the private key safely.</li>
</ol>
<h3>What other cryptocurrencies can OpenDime store?</h3>
<p>Currently, OpenDime only supports the classics, Bitcoin and Litecoin. They may add support for more coins in the future.</p>
<h3>Is OpenDime secure?</h3>
<p>OpenDime is secure until it is opened. The private key is completely covered until the security clip is broken off. Some hardware components and diodes are exposed on the outside but pose a minimal security risk if the OpenDime is kept in a safe environment such as a drawer or safe.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Digital BitBox</h2>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-9617" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/digital-bitbox-featured.jpg" alt="" width="293" height="226" /><br />
<em>image via Gadget Flow</em></p>
<p><a href="/visit/urg/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Digital Bitbox</a> is a hardware wallet created in Switzerland by Bitcoin Core creator Jonas Schnelli. Digital Bitbox aims to make coin storage as simple as possible by handling RNG and key storage so the user doesn’t need to worry about it. It does not feature a screen, so it is managed with a software interface once connected to a computer. Digital BitBox sells for €59 on their official website.</p>
<h3>How secure is Digital Bitbox?</h3>
<p>Digital Bitbox is considered to be impenetrable, as it utilizes encrypted USB communication, tamper-resistant microchips, and options such as two-factor authentication. Offline backups can be easily created using the Micro SD slot on the side of the device, which can add peace of mind in case the device is lost or stolen. The Digital BitBox is entirely open-source and the code can be viewed in its entirety on <a href="https://github.com/digitalbitbox" target="_blank">Github</a>. This adds a level of transparency to the Digital BitBox project which is unmatched by other hardware wallets.</p>
<h3>What other coins does Digital BitBox support?</h3>
<p>Digital BitBox support Bitcoin, Litecoin, Ethereum, Ethereum Classic and ERC20 tokens. They may add support for additional cryptocurrencies in the future.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>Depending on your needs, some hardware wallets may be better than others. For the majority of cryptocurrency holders, the <a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/ledger/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Ledger Nano S</a> or <a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/trezor/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">Trezor</a> will be ideal due to their impeccable security, ease of use, and somewhat broad coin support. They allow for easy daily use as well as safe long-term storage.</p>
<p>For exclusively long-term holds, a cheaper wallet such as a <a href="/visit/urg/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Digital BitBox</a> or <a href="/visit/trg/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">OpenDime</a> will suffice. These are not ideal for day-to-day transactional use though.</p>
<p>For users who want to transact with cryptocurrencies in person, something such as <a href="/visit/trg/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">OpenDime</a> will be the best, most cost-effective option.</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/top-five-crypto-hardware-wallets-review-and-comparison/">Top Five Crypto Hardware Wallets: Review and Comparison</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/top-five-crypto-hardware-wallets-review-and-comparison/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Claim Bitcoin Private?</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-private/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-private/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 19:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=3741</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Private (BTCP) is a hard fork of Bitcoin and ZClassic. It offers increased anonymity over Bitcoin and a larger block size which allows for quicker transactions speeds. Anyone who ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="How to Claim Bitcoin Private?" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-private/#more-3741">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">How to Claim Bitcoin Private?</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-private/">How to Claim Bitcoin Private?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://airdrops.io/bitcoin-private/">Bitcoin Private</a> (BTCP) is a hard fork of Bitcoin and ZClassic. It offers increased anonymity over Bitcoin and a larger block size which allows for quicker transactions speeds. Anyone who was holding Bitcoin or ZClassic on February 28th, 2018 during the block snapshots (511346 for BTC and 272991 for ZCL) is eligible to claim Bitcoin Private at a ratio of 1:1.</p>
<h2>Claim your Bitcoin Private on Supported Exchanges</h2>
<p>If you were holding your Bitcoins or ZClassic on an exchange that supports Bitcoin Private, then you won&#8217;t need to do anything to make your claim. Your account should have automatically been credited with BTCP at the time of the fork. During that time, the only exchanges that supported ZCL were Bittrex and Cryptopia, though due to their silence on the matter, it&#8217;s unclear whether either of them actually distributed BTCP. Currently, the exchanges supporting BTCP are:</p>
<ul>
<li>TradeSatoshi.com</li>
<li>Nanex</li>
<li>Octaex</li>
<li>Exrates</li>
<li>BarterDEX</li>
<li>HitBTC (listing in process)</li>
</ul>
<p>You can view the most current list of supported exchanges <a href="/visit/xm7/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here on Coinmarketcap</a>.</p>
<p>If you weren&#8217;t so lucky as to have your Bitcoins or ZClassic on a supported exchange, no problem! Follow the guide below to claim your Bitcoin Private in 5 minutes or less.</p>
<h2>Claim your Bitcoin Private with Coinomi<strong><br />
</strong></h2>
<p>Android and iPhone users can claim their BTCP easily with the Coinomi wallet app, available <a href="/visit/xc5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a>.</p>
<p>1. Download Coinomi if you don&#8217;t already have it.<br />
2. For safety reasons, we recommend moving your BTC and ZCL to a new wallet address before claiming. Your forked coins will remain in the original wallet address.<br />
3. Create a new Coinomi wallet or import your seed phrase (12-24 words) from your external wallet.<br />
4. Click on (+) COINS and add BTCP wallet with &#8220;<strong>M/44H/147H/0H</strong>&#8221; in the derivation path.</p>
<p>**If you’re attempting to import a private key from a paper wallet or QR code, you should click &#8220;Create New Wallet&#8221; in Coinomi and click &#8220;Sweep Paper Wallet&#8221; in the settings.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Claim Bitcoin Private with Electrum</h2>
<p>If you had trouble with the previous options, you can extract the private keys of your BTC or ZCL addresses using Electrum and try importing those into Coinomi. This is how to do it:</p>
<p>1. Download Electrum (either <a href="https://github.com/z-classic/electrum-zcl" target="_blank">ZCL</a>, <a href="/visit/1n7/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">BTC</a> or both depending on which coins you were holding during the fork)<br />
2. Create a new wallet (choose &#8220;Standard wallet&#8221;).<br />
3. Choose &#8220;I already have a seed&#8221; and create a new wallet with your seed phrase.<br />
4. Export the private keys (Wallet&gt;Private Keys&gt;Export) to a CSV file.<br />
5. In Coinomi, choose &#8220;Create a New Wallet.&#8221;<br />
6. Click on the menu at the top right and choose &#8220;Sweep wallet.&#8221;<br />
7. Enter your private keys and click &#8220;next.&#8221;<br />
8. Never share your private keys with anyone!<br />
9. If you prefer to keep your BTCP in Electrum, you can download the BTCP Electrum wallet from <a href="/visit/2n7/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">BTCPrivate.org</a>. Choose the one that is compatible with your operating system.</p>
<h2>How many ZClassic are in circulation and how many Bitcoin Private will there be after the fork?</h2>
<p>There are about 3 million ZCL in circulation. When the fork was initiated, the total Bitcoin Private put into circulation was the circulating supply of BTC plus ZCL (currently 20,311,925 BTCP).</p>
<h2>Where To Sell your Bitcoin Private</h2>
<p>Congratulations, you&#8217;ve claimed your Bitcoin Private coins! Now, what do you do with them?! If you don&#8217;t plan to HODL, you can deposit BTCP into TradeSatoshi or BarterDEX to sell it for BTC, USD or any altcoin you want! You can make a deposit by going to your funds tab and clicking &#8220;Deposit&#8221; or &#8220;(+)&#8221; next to Bitcoin Private. It will take a few confirmations for your funds to appear in your exchange account. You can track the progress of your transactions using the <a href="/visit/3n7/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Private Block Explorer</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-private/">How to Claim Bitcoin Private?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-private/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 06:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=8221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is MyEtherWallet Secure? MyEtherWallet (MEW) is a free and open-source interface for Ethereum and ERC20 tokens that allows users to directly interact with the Ethereum blockchain with just their web ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="Is MyEtherWallet Safe?" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/#more-8221">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/">Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="mceTemp"></div>
<h2>Is MyEtherWallet Secure?</h2>
<p><a href="/visit/6a/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">MyEtherWallet</a> (MEW) is a free and open-source interface for Ethereum and ERC20 tokens that allows users to directly interact</p>
<p>with the Ethereum blockchain with just their web browsers. It among the most popular sites for creating and managing Ethereum wallets, but is it safe??</p>
<p>Recently, MyEtherWallet was hit with an attack that redirected some of its servers to a malicious phishing site in Russia, draining the wallets of unsuspecting victims who used MEW during the hours of the hack. This left many users to question the safety of MyEtherWallet and whether they should continue to use it in the future.</p>
<h2>So, should you continue to use MEW?</h2>
<p>To answer this, we will first explain how MyEtherWallet operates. Creating a MEW account will generate a public key and a private key, neither of which are ever stored on the MyEtherWallet site.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-8274 alignright" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/mew-article-image.jpg" alt="" width="514" height="360" /><br />
It is the sole responsibility of the user to back up their keys in a safe and reliable place (offline). The user can then access and send their ETH through hardware wallets (TREZOR, Ledger Nano S) or directly with private keys, mnemonic phrases, or keystore files.</p>
<p>Through an exploit in Amazon’s “Route 53” hosting system, the hackers were able to intercept DNS requests for myetherwallet.com to make their own server appear to be the rightful owner of the address. From there, they were able to redirect traffic to their own “MyEtherWallet” clone site, where victims handed over their private keys and seed phrases thinking that they were on the real MEW site. Fortunately, MyEtherWallet identified the hijacked servers and quickly rectified the issue, and only a few thousand dollars worth of ETH was stolen.</p>
<p>Accessing your wallet with a private key, keystore file, or mnemonic phrase leaves you vulnerable to these kinds of attacks. If you happen to land on a phishing site through no fault of your own, you will unknowingly deliver full control of your account to the hijackers.</p>
<p><strong>The most secure way to access your MEW account, <em>by far</em>, is with a hardware wallet.</strong> Hardware wallets act as a master key, and feature added layers of security such as code scramblers to ensure that your private keys and phrases are never stolen from you. The codes are shown on the screen of the hardware wallet, rather than on the screen of your computer, so an onlooker will never be able to decipher your combinations. If you were to access a malicious site using a hardware wallet, the worst that a hijacker could do is redirect an outgoing transaction to his own wallet. This would be unfortunate, yes, but it’s a lot better than having your entire balance drained.</p>
<p><figure id="attachment_8278" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-8278" style="width: 676px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-8278" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/MEW-article-trezor.jpg" alt="" width="686" height="360" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-8278" class="wp-caption-text"><em>image via the official trezor.io website</em></figcaption></figure></p>
<p>Two hardware wallets that we highly recommend are the TREZOR and Ledger Nano S. They are robust and reliable hardware wallets that have not failed us yet. They allow for easy management and storage of Ethereum and many other coins including Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, DASH, ZCASH and more (Yes, you can store your ERC20s on them too)!</p>
<p>In short, MyEtherWallet is still safe to use and will remain one of the most popular ETH management platforms, but it’s important for users to understand the risks of inputting their private keys or passwords into any centralized website. Hackers are getting craftier every day, and there is always the possibility that they will learn to exploit even the most trusted sites such as MyEtherWallet. To have peace of mind that your keys will remain safe, buy yourself a hardware wallet and ditch the keystore files.</p>
<div class="link-btn"><a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/trezor/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">To look at TREZOR hardware wallets, click here</a></div>
<div class="link-btn"><a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/ledger/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">To look at Ledger Nano S hardware wallets, click here</a></div>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/">Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=3622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Gold (BTG) was first introduced to the world on October 24th, 2017. Though the altcoin looks and functions the same as Bitcoin, BTG&#8217;s mining algorithm makes it much easier ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="How to claim Bitcoin Gold?" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/#more-3622">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/">How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Gold (BTG) was first introduced to the world on October 24th, 2017. Though the altcoin looks and functions the same as Bitcoin, BTG&#8217;s mining algorithm makes it much easier to mine on consumer-accessible GPUs.</p>
<p>Anyone who was holding Bitcoin (BTC) at the time Bitcoin Gold was created is eligible to collect an amount of Bitcoin Gold equal to the amount of Bitcoin they were holding (1:1).</p>
<h2>Claim your Bitcoin Gold on Supported Exchanges</h2>
<p>If you had your Bitcoins on an exchange that supports Bitcoin Gold during the snapshot date, then good news! You don&#8217;t need to do anything. Your account will automatically be credited with the proportional amount of BTG. Here is a list of exchanges that support Bitcoin Gold:</p>
<ul>
<li><em>HitBTC</em></li>
<li>Binance</li>
<li><em>YoBit</em></li>
<li><em>Bleutrade</em></li>
<li>BitStar</li>
<li><em>Bitfinex</em></li>
<li>Coinnest</li>
<li><em>Gate.io</em></li>
<li>Okex</li>
<li><em>CEX.io</em></li>
<li><em>BitFlyer</em></li>
<li>Changelly</li>
<li><em>BitBay</em></li>
<li>Beatcoin</li>
<li><em>Change Now</em></li>
<li><em>Paribu</em></li>
<li>Abucoins</li>
<li><em>KKEX</em></li>
</ul>
<p>If you weren&#8217;t so lucky as to have your Bitcoins on a supported exchange, no problem! Follow the guide below to claim your Bitcoin Gold in 5 minutes or less.</p>
<h2><strong>Claim your Bitcoin Gold with a Hardware Wallet</strong></h2>
<p><em>TREZOR</em></p>
<p>1. Update your firmware <a href="/visit/vc5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a><br />
2. Use <a href="/visit/wc5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">this tool</a> to claim your BTG.</p>
<p><em>LEDGER NANO S<br />
</em><br />
1. Be sure yuo are using the most recent Ledger Wallet Bitcoin Chrome app (v1.9.9)<br />
2. Be sure you are using the most recent Ledger Nano S firmware (v1.3.1)<br />
3. Install the Bitcoin Gold app on your Ledger through the Ledger Manager.<br />
4. Run the Ledger Wallet Bitcoin Chrome app on your browser.<br />
5. Run the Bitcoin Gold app on your Ledger.<br />
6. Click on &#8220;BTG split tool&#8221; line on the Chrome app (below main options, next to &#8220;Need assistance?&#8221;)<br />
7. If you have BTC on the <strong>Legacy</strong> chain, choose <strong>Legacy</strong>. Otherwise choose <strong>Segwit</strong>.<br />
8. Allow the app to sync and you will find your BTG in the chain you chose in the previous step (Legacy/Segwit).</p>
<h2>Claim Bitcoin Gold with Coinomi</h2>
<p>For Android and iPhone users, you can easily claim your Bitcoin Gold using a wonderful wallet application called <a href="/visit/xc5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Coinomi</a>. Download the app and follow the steps below:</p>
<p>0. For safety reasons, we recommend moving your BTC to a fresh new wallet (with a new private key) before starting this process. You will be exposing the private key and seed phrase of your old wallet which will leave it vulnerable.<br />
1. Find your seed. This is the 12-24 word phrase you wrote down when you first created your wallet.<br />
2. Import your seed into Coinomi by choosing &#8220;Restore a wallet.&#8221; If you already use Coinomi, BACK UP YOUR EXISTING WALLET FIRST. This is extremely important as this process could wipe your current Coinomi data.<br />
3. Once your wallet is imported, click on &#8220;(+) COINS.&#8221;<br />
4. Add Bitcoin Gold. (depending on the wallet you are importing from, you may need to go to &#8220;Advanced Settings&#8221; and type &#8220;<strong>M/44H/0H/0H</strong>&#8221; into the Derivation Path (BIP32).<br />
5. Repeat the above process with any other eligible Bitcoin wallets you have.</p>
<p>**If you’re attempting to import a private key from a paper wallet or QR code, you should click &#8220;Create New Wallet&#8221; in Coinomi and click &#8220;Sweep Paper Wallet&#8221; in the settings.</p>
<h2>Claim Bitcoin Gold with Electrum</h2>
<p>If you had trouble with the previous options, you can extract the private keys of your Bitcoin addresses using Electrum and try importing those into Coinomi. This is how to do it:</p>
<p>1. Download Electrum.<br />
2. Create a new wallet (choose &#8220;Standard wallet&#8221;).<br />
3. Choose &#8220;I already have a seed&#8221; and create a new wallet with your seed phrase.<br />
4. Export the private keys (Wallet&gt;Private Keys&gt;Export) to a CSV file.<br />
5. In Coinomi, choose &#8220;Create a New Wallet.&#8221;<br />
6. Click on the menu in the top right and choose &#8220;Sweep wallet.&#8221;<br />
7. Enter your private keys and click &#8220;next.&#8221;<br />
8. Never share your private keys with anyone!</p>
<p>The process is as follows: Download Electrum Create a new wallet from your seed phrase Export the private keys of your wallet Write down the private key that had Bitcoins in them prior to the fork Create a Coinomi BTG wallet Sweep the private key into the Coinomi BTG wallet</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re having trouble understanding the process, or you just don&#8217;t feel like reading today, here is a nice little tutorial video:</p>
<p><iframe loading="lazy" title="BITCOIN GOLD TUTORIAL FOR COINOMI ANDROID!! CLAIM IN 5 MINUTES OR LESS" width="1130" height="636" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PUSuEHl9Qfo?start=4&#038;feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<h2>Where To Sell your Bitcoin Gold</h2>
<p>Congratulations, you&#8217;ve claimed your Bitcoin Gold coins! Now, what do you do with them?! If you don&#8217;t plan to HODL, you can deposit BTG into HitBTC or Bittrex to sell it for BTC, USD, or any altcoin you want! You can make a deposit by going to your funds tab and clicking &#8220;Deposit&#8221; or &#8220;(+)&#8221; next to Bitcoin Gold (do not confuse BTG with BTC). It will take a few confirmations for your funds to appear in your exchange account. You can track the progress of your transactions using the <a href="/visit/0d5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Gold Block Explorer</a>.</p>
<p>You can find the full list of Bitcoin Gold exchanges <a href="/visit/nl7/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here on Coinmarketcap</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/">How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[airdropadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 22:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=3633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is message signing? Message signing is a way for you to prove ownership of a particular address, and demonstrate you have control of the funds. Why sign? Signing is ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/#more-3633">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/">How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>What is message signing?</h1>
<p>Message signing is a way for you to prove ownership of a particular address, and demonstrate you have control of the funds.</p>
<h2 id="732d" class="graf graf--h4 graf-after--p">Why sign?</h2>
<p>Signing is an easy way of assuring that something is being done by the correct person or contract. Unlike physical signatures, digital signatures cannot be faked so you can always be sure that an action was completed by the correct person.</p>
<p>Etherscan</p>
<p>Message signing can be done easily with <a href="/visit/8wc/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Etherscan</a>’s “Verify New Message Signature” feature.</p>
<p>1. Go to the <a href="/visit/3ig/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><em>Verify New Message Signature</em> tool</a>.<br />
2. Provide the Ethereum address you would like to sign with.<br />
3. Provide the message Signature hash and the original message that is being signed.<br />
4. Click Verify and Save from the drop-down menu.<br />
5. Submit.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-9436 aligncenter" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/etherscan-sign-example.png" alt="" width="721" height="354" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Blockchain App</h2>
<p>In the popular wallet app, <a href="/visit/4ig/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Blockchain</a>, message signing is quite simple. To sign a message,</p>
<p>1. Go to <em>Settings -&gt; Addresses</em><br />
2. Scroll down to choose the desired address.<br />
3. Click <em>More Options -&gt; Sign Message.</em></p>
<p><em>Note: this is currently only available for imported addresses, but will be added to all addresses in the future. </em></p>
<h2>Technical Explanation</h2>
<p>The following method creates an Ethereum-specific signature with:<br />
<strong><em>sign(keccak256(&#8220;\x19Ethereum Signed Message:\n&#8221; + len(message) + message))).</em></strong></p>
<p>Adding a prefix to the message will make the signature recognizable as an Ethereum-specific signature. This would prevent any fraud or misuse where a malicious DAPP could sign random data (such as a transaction) and use the signature to impersonate the victim. <strong><em>Note:</em></strong><em> the address to sign with should be unlocked for this to work. </em></p>
<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p>account, message</p>
<ol>
<li><strong><em>DATA</em>, 20 Bytes</strong> = address</li>
<li><strong><em>DATA</em>, N Bytes</strong> = message to sign</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Returns</strong></p>
<pre><code>DATA: Signature</code></pre>
<p><strong>Example</strong></p>
<pre><code>
// Request
curl -X POST --data '{"jsonrpc":"2.0","method":"eth_sign","params":["0x9b2055d370f73ec7d8a03e965129118dc8f5bf83", "0xdeadbeaf"],"id":1}'
// Result
{
"id":1,
"jsonrpc": "2.0",
"result": "0xa3f20717a250c2b0b729b7e5becbff67fdaef7e0699da4de7ca5895b02a170a12d887fd3b17bfdce3481f10bea41f45ba9f709d39ce8325427b57afcfc994cee1b"
}
</code></pre>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/">How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
