<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog Archive &#187; airdrops.io</title>
	<atom:link href="https://airdrops.io/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description>Your Trusted Crypto Intelligence Hub: From Airdrops to Advanced Strategies</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 11:51:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/03/apple-touch-icon-152x152-150x150.png</url>
	<title>Blog Archive &#187; airdrops.io</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Al]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 00:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Allgemein]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[airdrop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bartio]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bartio testnet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bera]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[berachain]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[testnet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=894764</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Introduction to Berachain Berachain is an emerging blockchain network that has garnered significant attention in the cryptocurrency space. With a substantial $142 million investment from reputable venture capital firms, Berachain ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/#more-894764">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/">Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Introduction to Berachain</h2>



<p><strong>Berachain</strong> is an emerging blockchain network that has garnered significant attention in the cryptocurrency space. With a substantial $142 million investment from reputable venture capital firms, Berachain introduces a novel consensus mechanism called Proof of Liquidity (POL). This innovative approach sets it apart from traditional Proof of Work (PoW) and Proof of Stake (PoS) systems.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Understanding Proof of Liquidity (POL)</h2>



<p>Unlike Bitcoin&#8217;s PoW or Ethereum&#8217;s PoS, Berachain&#8217;s POL mechanism allows users to participate in network security and transaction processing by locking liquidity on the network. This unique approach not only ensures network stability but also inherently increases the Total Value Locked (TVL), benefiting the ecosystem&#8217;s overall health.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Key Tokens in the Berachain Ecosystem</h2>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>BERA</strong>: The native token used for gas fees and network transactions.</li>



<li><strong>HONEY</strong>: A native stablecoin within the Berachain network.</li>



<li><strong>BGT</strong>: A governance token earned through providing liquidity, which can be delegated for voting rights.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Airdrop Farming Strategy for Berachain</h2>



<p>To position yourself for potential airdrops, consider the following strategies:</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">1. Increase Transaction Count</h3>



<p>Aim for 200-300 organic transactions, with some users targeting up to 500. This activity demonstrates genuine engagement with the network.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">2. Utilize Faucets Effectively</h3>



<p>Berachain&#8217;s team has emphasized the importance of faucets in this testnet. Key faucets include:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><a href="/visit/64t2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bartio Faucet</a> (8-hour cooldown)</li>



<li><a href="/visit/6xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Kodiak Finance Faucet</a> (3-hour cooldown)</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">3. Provide Liquidity and Farm BGT</h3>



<p>Use acquired BERA to provide liquidity on <a href="/visit/7xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bex</a>, focusing on pools with high APY. This strategy allows you to earn BGT, a non-tradable token crucial for potential airdrop qualification.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">4. Engage with the Ecosystem</h3>



<p>Interact with various Berachain platforms:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><a href="/visit/8xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Station</a> for BGT farming and delegation</li>



<li><a href="/visit/vxp2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Honey</a> for minting the network&#8217;s stablecoin</li>



<li><a href="/visit/9xt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bend</a> for borrowing</li>



<li><a href="/visit/axt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">BERPS</a> for perpetual trading</li>



<li>Beranames: It is the official name service for Berachain, offering a human-readable address system for blockchain transactions. Users can mint unique NFT names, personalize their Berachain ID, and create subdomains for contracts, wallets, and more.<br>Beranames is running a points campaign for its early users, which may factor into future airdrops when Berachain goes live. Participating in the Beranames ecosystem demonstrates active engagement and could potentially increase your chances of qualifying for future airdrops.<br>For a detailed guide on how to participate in Beranames and earn points, refer to <a href="https://airdrops.io/beranames/">our comprehensive guide</a>.</li>
</ul>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">5. Diversify Transactions</h3>



<p>Use <a href="/visit/bxt2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Intract</a> for varied transaction types, ensuring a well-rounded activity profile.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">6. Discord Engagement</h3>



<p>Join the <a href="https://discord.gg/berachain" target="_blank">Berachain Discord</a> and actively participate in community channels. Engage thoughtfully to potentially receive BERA tips from community whales.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">7. Claim and Delegate BGT</h3>



<p>Regularly claim your farmed BGT and delegate it to validators, demonstrating long-term commitment to the network&#8217;s governance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Conclusion</h2>



<p>Berachain&#8217;s innovative POL mechanism and robust ecosystem present unique opportunities for airdrop farmers. By engaging genuinely across various platforms, providing liquidity, and actively participating in the community, you can optimize your chances for potential future rewards.</p>



<p>Remember, while these strategies can enhance your position, there&#8217;s no guarantee of airdrops. Always conduct your own research and invest responsibly. Also make sure to read our full Airdrop Guide <a href="https://airdrops.io/berachain/">Here</a>.</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/">Berachain Airdrop Farming Guide: Maximizing Your Potential in the Innovative POL Ecosystem</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/berachain-airdrop-farming-guide-pol-ecosystem/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Jamie]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 12:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=650827</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>ZkSync was the most highly anticipated airdrop in recent years and one of the most generous, distributing 17.5% of the total supply to eligible users and builders. While over 6 ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/#more-650827">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/">A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZkSync was the most highly anticipated airdrop in recent years and one of the most generous, distributing 17.5% of the total supply to eligible users and builders. While over 6 million wallets interacted with zkSync’s Layer 2, just over </span><a href="/visit/g0q2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">695,000 wallets were included</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. Despite many missing out, ZK is one of the most widely distributed airdrops. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s not over for ZK farmers though. A further 49.5% of the supply will go to the community. In an upcoming post we’ll outline how to position for these further drops. In this post, we’ll take a look at 5 lessons from the ZK airdrop to see what farmers can learn from this event and how they can apply these takeaways to other Layer 2’s that are yet to </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">tokenize</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">. </span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #1: Bridge In and Bridge Often, But Don’t Bridge Out</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZK took a serious departure from the playbook of other Layer 2 airdrops, such as Arbitrum. Transaction volume was not a qualifier at all! What they did introduce however, which we haven’t really seen much of in airdrops up until now, is a multiplier based on your time-weighted average balance (TWAB). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A TWAB approach favours smaller farmers who have less funds as compared to previous airdrops. It opens up the possibility that users with smaller pockets can maintain a larger TWAB than a mercenary farmer with more capital who only parked funds on zkSync for a much shorter time period. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Specifically, zkSync users needed a time-weighted average balance of $50 to qualify, with a larger TWAB boosting to their allocation. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The few lessons farmers should take from this: </span></p>
<ol>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">Users who stick around are rewarded: When bridging funds to a Layer 2, try to keep your funds there for as long as possible.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-weight: 400;">It’s a marathon, not a sprint: Bridge an initial amount and then bridge more funds over time. </span></li>
<li>Actively participate in DeFi protocols: Deposit these funds into a DeFi liquidity pool to earn yield and increase your chances of qualifying.</li>
</ol>
<h2><b>Lesson #2: HODL native tokens and NFTs</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Always buy and HOLD native tokens and NFTs for the Layer 2s you’re farming. You can use </span><a href="/visit/aoq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">DeFiLlama</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to see the top protocols for the chain you’re farming and see if they have a token. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZkSync users who held $50 or more in native tokens received a multiplier, specifically the top 7 projects ranked by market capitalisation. Another multiplier was given if a ZkSync native NFT collection was held at snapshot. On top of both of these actions, you should also trade at least 10 different ERC-20 tokens on the L2s you’re farming, as this was an eligibility criteria for ZK. </span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #3: Turn on Notifications on X for the Project You’re Farming</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">As well as DeFiLlama, you can also turn on notifications for the official account of a Layer 2 on X to see what they post about. They’ll often promote native tokens and NFT collections. It’s recommended to take action based on what a project tweets about, as these can be subtle hints of which on-chain activities may be rewarded with an airdrop.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For example, the </span><a href="/visit/boq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">official zkSync account</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> on X frequently tweeted about Paymaster function, which allows you to pay gas fees with tokens other than ETH. Many airdrop farmers speculated that using Paymaster frequently would be a possible criteria or multiplier, and they turned out to be right! </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Similarly, you want to see what the official account of a Layer 2 is promoting and act on these cues to bag a larger airdrop!</span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #4: Be active on-chain and try new things</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A total of 102.375 million ZK tokens were distributed to experimental, on-chain communities, highlighting the importance of being active on-chain and trying new things. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">BONSAI and DEGEN claimers both got a ZK allocation for simply being early to innovative on-chain communities. BONSAI was airdropped to certain Lens ecosystem users, a web3 social media alternative to Twitter and YouTube. DEGEN is the unofficial coin of Farcaster, another decentralized social media platform which awarded early adopters. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">It&#8217;s difficult to be early in the next big thing! But you should always be on the lookout, be active on-chain and try new things to maximise your airdrop exposure. You never know what interactions may end up giving you an unexpected surprise later down the line. </span></p>
<h2><b>Lesson #5: Attend Crypto Events and Acquire POAPs</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Did you know that some people receive ZK tokens without being active on-chain? If you had attended one of seven events where zkSync was giving away POAPs, then you could have gotten a higher allocation. POAPs are short for proof of attendance protocols and they are on-chain badges proving you were at an event. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">For example, if you had visited ZkSync’s booth at ETH Denver and collected the POAP, you’d have been eligible for the builders allocation. Some of these events even happened after the snapshot. For example, addresses that held POAPs from smaller events, like the zkSync meetup in Brussels, were also given a token allocation.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The takeaway from this is that you should look to attend upcoming events, such as </span><a href="/visit/coq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">EthCC</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> in Brussels (July 8th-11th). It&#8217;s likely that many teams from tokenless projects will be present and there will be many POAPs to collect. Alternatively, you can look for events closer to home by using sites like </span><a href="/visit/doq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">EventBrite</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="/visit/eoq2/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Meetup</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and also by monitoring a project’s X account. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">ZkSync gives us yet another case study for airdrops, along with Arbitrum and StarkNet, that provides very useful information on what to focus on when farming the upcoming tokens for L2s like </span><a href="https://airdrops.io/scroll/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Scroll</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://airdrops.io/linea/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Linea</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> or </span><a href="https://airdrops.io/karak/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Karak</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">. By taking these 5 lessons and applying them to your farming, you should have no problems qualifying for the next big drops! </span></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/">A Farmer&#8217;s Reflection on the ZK Airdrop</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/a-farmers-reflection-on-the-zk-airdrop/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 10:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=9887</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Here is a schedule showing the dates of distribution for all of the Airdrops.io exclusive airdrops. ICOs that host airdrops almost never distribute tokens until their main sale is over. This ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/#more-9887">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/">Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here is a schedule showing the dates of distribution for all of the Airdrops.io exclusive airdrops.</p>
<p><div id="tablepress-2-scroll-wrapper" class="tablepress-scroll-wrapper">

<table id="tablepress-2" class="tablepress tablepress-id-2 tablepress-responsive">
<thead>
<tr class="row-1 odd">
	<th class="column-1">Project</th><th class="column-2">Airdrop Started</th><th class="column-3">Distribution Date</th><th class="column-4">Link</th>
</tr>
</thead>
<tbody class="row-hover">
<tr class="row-2 even">
	<td class="column-1">ImmVRse</td><td class="column-2">06/19/2018</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/immvrse/">ImmVRse</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-3 odd">
	<td class="column-1">HelloGold</td><td class="column-2">06/09/2018</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/hellogold/">HelloGold</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-4 even">
	<td class="column-1">Profede</td><td class="column-2">05/15/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/profede/">Profede</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-5 odd">
	<td class="column-1">EthicHub Twitter</td><td class="column-2">04/17/18</td><td class="column-3">After end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/ethichub-twitter/">EthicHub Twitter</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-6 even">
	<td class="column-1">EthicHub Telegram</td><td class="column-2">04/05/18</td><td class="column-3">After end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/ethichub/">EthicHub Telegram</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-7 odd">
	<td class="column-1">dApp Builder</td><td class="column-2">04/19/18</td><td class="column-3">After end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/dapp-builder/">dApp Builder</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-8 even">
	<td class="column-1">Pecunio</td><td class="column-2">04/05/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/pecunio/">Pecunio</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-9 odd">
	<td class="column-1">Lamoneda</td><td class="column-2">05/24/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/lamoneda/">Lamoneda</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-10 even">
	<td class="column-1">BitRewards</td><td class="column-2">04/06/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/bitrewards">BitRewards</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-11 odd">
	<td class="column-1">Apollo Currency</td><td class="column-2">04/30/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/apollo-currency/">Apollo</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-12 even">
	<td class="column-1">Hyperbridge</td><td class="column-2">06/23/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/hyperbridge/">Hyperbridge</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-13 odd">
	<td class="column-1">moolyacoin</td><td class="column-2">06/22/18</td><td class="column-3">2 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/moolyacoin/">moolyacoin</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-14 even">
	<td class="column-1">Blackbox Foundation<br />
</td><td class="column-2">02/07/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/blackbox-foundation/">Blackbox Foundation<br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-15 odd">
	<td class="column-1">ODIN</td><td class="column-2">12/07/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/odin/">ODIN</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-16 even">
	<td class="column-1">Beam</td><td class="column-2">06/08/18</td><td class="column-3">30 days after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/beam/">Beam</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-17 odd">
	<td class="column-1">RedCab</td><td class="column-2">14/08/18</td><td class="column-3">30 days after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/redcab-exclusive/">RedCab</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-18 even">
	<td class="column-1">dClinic</td><td class="column-2">20/08/18</td><td class="column-3">2 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/dclinic/">dClinic</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-19 odd">
	<td class="column-1">XTribe</td><td class="column-2">22/08/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/xtribe/">XTribe</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-20 even">
	<td class="column-1">IUNO</td><td class="column-2">10/09/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/iuno/">IUNO</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-21 odd">
	<td class="column-1">Triphop</td><td class="column-2">11/09/18</td><td class="column-3">5 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/triphop/">Triphop</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-22 even">
	<td class="column-1">MorLabs</td><td class="column-2">11/09/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/morlabs/">MorLabs</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-23 odd">
	<td class="column-1">AIVON</td><td class="column-2">20/09/18</td><td class="column-3">ICO canceled 🙁</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/aivon/">AIVON</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-24 even">
	<td class="column-1">HiLynk</td><td class="column-2">8/10/18</td><td class="column-3">6 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/hilynk/">HiLynk</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-25 odd">
	<td class="column-1">London Block Exchange<br />
</td><td class="column-2">12/10/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/london-block-exchange/">London Block Exchange<br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-26 even">
	<td class="column-1">V Systems</td><td class="column-2">06/11/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/v-systems/">V Systems<br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-27 odd">
	<td class="column-1">FST Network<br />
</td><td class="column-2">06/12/18</td><td class="column-3">6 weeks after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/fst-network/">FST Network <br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-28 even">
	<td class="column-1">Bluenote</td><td class="column-2">13/12/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/bluenote/">Bluenote <br />
</a></td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-29 odd">
	<td class="column-1">VANM</td><td class="column-2">19/12/18</td><td class="column-3">Distribution is ongoing ⌛</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/vanm/">VANM<br />
</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-30 even">
	<td class="column-1">NOIA Network<br />
</td><td class="column-2">1/5/19</td><td class="column-3">3 months  after end of token sale</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/noia-network/">NOIA Network<br />
</td>
</tr>
<tr class="row-31 odd">
	<td class="column-1">COINCOME</td><td class="column-2">10/7/19</td><td class="column-3">Distribution finished ✅</td><td class="column-4"><a href="https://airdrops.io/coincome/">COINCOME<br />
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>

</div><!-- #tablepress-2 from cache --></p>
<p>ICOs that host airdrops almost never distribute tokens until their main sale is over. This is to prevent airdrop claimers from dumping their rewards on decentralized exchanges and decimating the token&#8217;s price before the real investors have a chance to trade. Also, the total supply of a token us often determined after the token sale, when all unsold tokens are burned.</p>
<p>If you did not receive your airdrop tokens, you should check our FAQ section, &#8220;<a href="https://airdrops.io/faq/why-didnt-i-receive-my-airdrop/">Why didn&#8217;t I receive my airdrop?</a>&#8220;</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/exclusive-airdrop-distribution-schedule/">Exclusive Airdrop Distribution Schedule</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 06:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=8221</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Is MyEtherWallet Secure? MyEtherWallet (MEW) is a free and open-source interface for Ethereum and ERC20 tokens that allows users to directly interact with the Ethereum blockchain with just their web ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="Is MyEtherWallet Safe?" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/#more-8221">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/">Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="mceTemp"></div>
<h2>Is MyEtherWallet Secure?</h2>
<p><a href="/visit/6a/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">MyEtherWallet</a> (MEW) is a free and open-source interface for Ethereum and ERC20 tokens that allows users to directly interact</p>
<p>with the Ethereum blockchain with just their web browsers. It among the most popular sites for creating and managing Ethereum wallets, but is it safe??</p>
<p>Recently, MyEtherWallet was hit with an attack that redirected some of its servers to a malicious phishing site in Russia, draining the wallets of unsuspecting victims who used MEW during the hours of the hack. This left many users to question the safety of MyEtherWallet and whether they should continue to use it in the future.</p>
<h2>So, should you continue to use MEW?</h2>
<p>To answer this, we will first explain how MyEtherWallet operates. Creating a MEW account will generate a public key and a private key, neither of which are ever stored on the MyEtherWallet site.</p>
<p><img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-8274 alignright" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/mew-article-image.jpg" alt="" width="514" height="360" /><br />
It is the sole responsibility of the user to back up their keys in a safe and reliable place (offline). The user can then access and send their ETH through hardware wallets (TREZOR, Ledger Nano S) or directly with private keys, mnemonic phrases, or keystore files.</p>
<p>Through an exploit in Amazon’s “Route 53” hosting system, the hackers were able to intercept DNS requests for myetherwallet.com to make their own server appear to be the rightful owner of the address. From there, they were able to redirect traffic to their own “MyEtherWallet” clone site, where victims handed over their private keys and seed phrases thinking that they were on the real MEW site. Fortunately, MyEtherWallet identified the hijacked servers and quickly rectified the issue, and only a few thousand dollars worth of ETH was stolen.</p>
<p>Accessing your wallet with a private key, keystore file, or mnemonic phrase leaves you vulnerable to these kinds of attacks. If you happen to land on a phishing site through no fault of your own, you will unknowingly deliver full control of your account to the hijackers.</p>
<p><strong>The most secure way to access your MEW account, <em>by far</em>, is with a hardware wallet.</strong> Hardware wallets act as a master key, and feature added layers of security such as code scramblers to ensure that your private keys and phrases are never stolen from you. The codes are shown on the screen of the hardware wallet, rather than on the screen of your computer, so an onlooker will never be able to decipher your combinations. If you were to access a malicious site using a hardware wallet, the worst that a hijacker could do is redirect an outgoing transaction to his own wallet. This would be unfortunate, yes, but it’s a lot better than having your entire balance drained.</p>
<p><figure id="attachment_8278" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-8278" style="width: 676px" class="wp-caption alignleft"><img decoding="async" class="wp-image-8278" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/05/MEW-article-trezor.jpg" alt="" width="686" height="360" /><figcaption id="caption-attachment-8278" class="wp-caption-text"><em>image via the official trezor.io website</em></figcaption></figure></p>
<p>Two hardware wallets that we highly recommend are the TREZOR and Ledger Nano S. They are robust and reliable hardware wallets that have not failed us yet. They allow for easy management and storage of Ethereum and many other coins including Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, DASH, ZCASH and more (Yes, you can store your ERC20s on them too)!</p>
<p>In short, MyEtherWallet is still safe to use and will remain one of the most popular ETH management platforms, but it’s important for users to understand the risks of inputting their private keys or passwords into any centralized website. Hackers are getting craftier every day, and there is always the possibility that they will learn to exploit even the most trusted sites such as MyEtherWallet. To have peace of mind that your keys will remain safe, buy yourself a hardware wallet and ditch the keystore files.</p>
<div class="link-btn"><a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/trezor/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">To look at TREZOR hardware wallets, click here</a></div>
<div class="link-btn"><a href="https://airdrops.io/goto/ledger/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank">To look at Ledger Nano S hardware wallets, click here</a></div>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/">Is MyEtherWallet Safe?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/is-myetherwallet-safe/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Austin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=3622</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Gold (BTG) was first introduced to the world on October 24th, 2017. Though the altcoin looks and functions the same as Bitcoin, BTG&#8217;s mining algorithm makes it much easier ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="How to claim Bitcoin Gold?" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/#more-3622">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/">How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bitcoin Gold (BTG) was first introduced to the world on October 24th, 2017. Though the altcoin looks and functions the same as Bitcoin, BTG&#8217;s mining algorithm makes it much easier to mine on consumer-accessible GPUs.</p>
<p>Anyone who was holding Bitcoin (BTC) at the time Bitcoin Gold was created is eligible to collect an amount of Bitcoin Gold equal to the amount of Bitcoin they were holding (1:1).</p>
<h2>Claim your Bitcoin Gold on Supported Exchanges</h2>
<p>If you had your Bitcoins on an exchange that supports Bitcoin Gold during the snapshot date, then good news! You don&#8217;t need to do anything. Your account will automatically be credited with the proportional amount of BTG. Here is a list of exchanges that support Bitcoin Gold:</p>
<ul>
<li><em>HitBTC</em></li>
<li>Binance</li>
<li><em>YoBit</em></li>
<li><em>Bleutrade</em></li>
<li>BitStar</li>
<li><em>Bitfinex</em></li>
<li>Coinnest</li>
<li><em>Gate.io</em></li>
<li>Okex</li>
<li><em>CEX.io</em></li>
<li><em>BitFlyer</em></li>
<li>Changelly</li>
<li><em>BitBay</em></li>
<li>Beatcoin</li>
<li><em>Change Now</em></li>
<li><em>Paribu</em></li>
<li>Abucoins</li>
<li><em>KKEX</em></li>
</ul>
<p>If you weren&#8217;t so lucky as to have your Bitcoins on a supported exchange, no problem! Follow the guide below to claim your Bitcoin Gold in 5 minutes or less.</p>
<h2><strong>Claim your Bitcoin Gold with a Hardware Wallet</strong></h2>
<p><em>TREZOR</em></p>
<p>1. Update your firmware <a href="/visit/vc5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here</a><br />
2. Use <a href="/visit/wc5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">this tool</a> to claim your BTG.</p>
<p><em>LEDGER NANO S<br />
</em><br />
1. Be sure yuo are using the most recent Ledger Wallet Bitcoin Chrome app (v1.9.9)<br />
2. Be sure you are using the most recent Ledger Nano S firmware (v1.3.1)<br />
3. Install the Bitcoin Gold app on your Ledger through the Ledger Manager.<br />
4. Run the Ledger Wallet Bitcoin Chrome app on your browser.<br />
5. Run the Bitcoin Gold app on your Ledger.<br />
6. Click on &#8220;BTG split tool&#8221; line on the Chrome app (below main options, next to &#8220;Need assistance?&#8221;)<br />
7. If you have BTC on the <strong>Legacy</strong> chain, choose <strong>Legacy</strong>. Otherwise choose <strong>Segwit</strong>.<br />
8. Allow the app to sync and you will find your BTG in the chain you chose in the previous step (Legacy/Segwit).</p>
<h2>Claim Bitcoin Gold with Coinomi</h2>
<p>For Android and iPhone users, you can easily claim your Bitcoin Gold using a wonderful wallet application called <a href="/visit/xc5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Coinomi</a>. Download the app and follow the steps below:</p>
<p>0. For safety reasons, we recommend moving your BTC to a fresh new wallet (with a new private key) before starting this process. You will be exposing the private key and seed phrase of your old wallet which will leave it vulnerable.<br />
1. Find your seed. This is the 12-24 word phrase you wrote down when you first created your wallet.<br />
2. Import your seed into Coinomi by choosing &#8220;Restore a wallet.&#8221; If you already use Coinomi, BACK UP YOUR EXISTING WALLET FIRST. This is extremely important as this process could wipe your current Coinomi data.<br />
3. Once your wallet is imported, click on &#8220;(+) COINS.&#8221;<br />
4. Add Bitcoin Gold. (depending on the wallet you are importing from, you may need to go to &#8220;Advanced Settings&#8221; and type &#8220;<strong>M/44H/0H/0H</strong>&#8221; into the Derivation Path (BIP32).<br />
5. Repeat the above process with any other eligible Bitcoin wallets you have.</p>
<p>**If you’re attempting to import a private key from a paper wallet or QR code, you should click &#8220;Create New Wallet&#8221; in Coinomi and click &#8220;Sweep Paper Wallet&#8221; in the settings.</p>
<h2>Claim Bitcoin Gold with Electrum</h2>
<p>If you had trouble with the previous options, you can extract the private keys of your Bitcoin addresses using Electrum and try importing those into Coinomi. This is how to do it:</p>
<p>1. Download Electrum.<br />
2. Create a new wallet (choose &#8220;Standard wallet&#8221;).<br />
3. Choose &#8220;I already have a seed&#8221; and create a new wallet with your seed phrase.<br />
4. Export the private keys (Wallet&gt;Private Keys&gt;Export) to a CSV file.<br />
5. In Coinomi, choose &#8220;Create a New Wallet.&#8221;<br />
6. Click on the menu in the top right and choose &#8220;Sweep wallet.&#8221;<br />
7. Enter your private keys and click &#8220;next.&#8221;<br />
8. Never share your private keys with anyone!</p>
<p>The process is as follows: Download Electrum Create a new wallet from your seed phrase Export the private keys of your wallet Write down the private key that had Bitcoins in them prior to the fork Create a Coinomi BTG wallet Sweep the private key into the Coinomi BTG wallet</p>
<p>If you&#8217;re having trouble understanding the process, or you just don&#8217;t feel like reading today, here is a nice little tutorial video:</p>
<p><iframe title="BITCOIN GOLD TUTORIAL FOR COINOMI ANDROID!! CLAIM IN 5 MINUTES OR LESS" width="1130" height="636" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PUSuEHl9Qfo?start=4&#038;feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<h2>Where To Sell your Bitcoin Gold</h2>
<p>Congratulations, you&#8217;ve claimed your Bitcoin Gold coins! Now, what do you do with them?! If you don&#8217;t plan to HODL, you can deposit BTG into HitBTC or Bittrex to sell it for BTC, USD, or any altcoin you want! You can make a deposit by going to your funds tab and clicking &#8220;Deposit&#8221; or &#8220;(+)&#8221; next to Bitcoin Gold (do not confuse BTG with BTC). It will take a few confirmations for your funds to appear in your exchange account. You can track the progress of your transactions using the <a href="/visit/0d5/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Bitcoin Gold Block Explorer</a>.</p>
<p>You can find the full list of Bitcoin Gold exchanges <a href="/visit/nl7/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">here on Coinmarketcap</a>.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/">How to claim Bitcoin Gold?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/how-to-claim-bitcoin-gold/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</title>
		<link>https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/</link>
					<comments>https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[airdropadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 22:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://airdrops.io/?p=3633</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What is message signing? Message signing is a way for you to prove ownership of a particular address, and demonstrate you have control of the funds. Why sign? Signing is ... </p>
<p class="read-more-container"><a title="How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?" class="read-more button" href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/#more-3633">Read more<span class="screen-reader-text">How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</span></a></p>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/">How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>What is message signing?</h1>
<p>Message signing is a way for you to prove ownership of a particular address, and demonstrate you have control of the funds.</p>
<h2 id="732d" class="graf graf--h4 graf-after--p">Why sign?</h2>
<p>Signing is an easy way of assuring that something is being done by the correct person or contract. Unlike physical signatures, digital signatures cannot be faked so you can always be sure that an action was completed by the correct person.</p>
<p>Etherscan</p>
<p>Message signing can be done easily with <a href="/visit/8wc/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Etherscan</a>’s “Verify New Message Signature” feature.</p>
<p>1. Go to the <a href="/visit/3ig/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"><em>Verify New Message Signature</em> tool</a>.<br />
2. Provide the Ethereum address you would like to sign with.<br />
3. Provide the message Signature hash and the original message that is being signed.<br />
4. Click Verify and Save from the drop-down menu.<br />
5. Submit.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="wp-image-9436 aligncenter" src="https://noelwest.github.io/wp-content/uploads/2018/04/etherscan-sign-example.png" alt="" width="721" height="354" /></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<h2>Blockchain App</h2>
<p>In the popular wallet app, <a href="/visit/4ig/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">Blockchain</a>, message signing is quite simple. To sign a message,</p>
<p>1. Go to <em>Settings -&gt; Addresses</em><br />
2. Scroll down to choose the desired address.<br />
3. Click <em>More Options -&gt; Sign Message.</em></p>
<p><em>Note: this is currently only available for imported addresses, but will be added to all addresses in the future. </em></p>
<h2>Technical Explanation</h2>
<p>The following method creates an Ethereum-specific signature with:<br />
<strong><em>sign(keccak256(&#8220;\x19Ethereum Signed Message:\n&#8221; + len(message) + message))).</em></strong></p>
<p>Adding a prefix to the message will make the signature recognizable as an Ethereum-specific signature. This would prevent any fraud or misuse where a malicious DAPP could sign random data (such as a transaction) and use the signature to impersonate the victim. <strong><em>Note:</em></strong><em> the address to sign with should be unlocked for this to work. </em></p>
<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p>account, message</p>
<ol>
<li><strong><em>DATA</em>, 20 Bytes</strong> = address</li>
<li><strong><em>DATA</em>, N Bytes</strong> = message to sign</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Returns</strong></p>
<pre><code>DATA: Signature</code></pre>
<p><strong>Example</strong></p>
<pre><code>
// Request
curl -X POST --data '{"jsonrpc":"2.0","method":"eth_sign","params":["0x9b2055d370f73ec7d8a03e965129118dc8f5bf83", "0xdeadbeaf"],"id":1}'
// Result
{
"id":1,
"jsonrpc": "2.0",
"result": "0xa3f20717a250c2b0b729b7e5becbff67fdaef7e0699da4de7ca5895b02a170a12d887fd3b17bfdce3481f10bea41f45ba9f709d39ce8325427b57afcfc994cee1b"
}
</code></pre>
<p>Der Beitrag <a href="https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/">How to sign or verify messages to prove address ownership?</a> erschien zuerst auf <a href="https://airdrops.io">airdrops.io</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://airdrops.io/how-to-sign-or-verify-messages-to-prove-address-ownership/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
